{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Electric Appliance Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/39763/":{"taskOID":39763,"originalTaskOID":39763,"setID":305,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3034,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Appliance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which appliances you would like to be installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2643,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freezer (chest)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (chest)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2644,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Freezer (upright)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (upright)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3838,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","answerDisplayText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2095,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2640,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5101,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Refrigerator/freezer","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator/freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6674,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Ventilation hood","answerDisplayText":"Ventilation hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6751,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Wall oven","answerDisplayText":"Wall oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5352,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3253,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install in new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install in new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5277,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5276,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in new location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500700,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the appliances for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the appliances for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3034,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Appliance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which appliances you would like to be installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2643,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freezer (chest)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (chest)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2644,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Freezer (upright)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (upright)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3838,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","answerDisplayText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2095,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2640,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5101,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Refrigerator/freezer","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator/freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6674,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Ventilation hood","answerDisplayText":"Ventilation hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6751,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Wall oven","answerDisplayText":"Wall oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2643,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freezer (chest)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (chest)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2644,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Freezer (upright)","answerDisplayText":"Freezer (upright)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3838,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","answerDisplayText":"Microwave/wall oven combination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2095,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Drop-in / slide-in range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2640,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding range (stove and oven combination)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5101,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Refrigerator/freezer","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator/freezer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6674,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Ventilation hood","answerDisplayText":"Ventilation hood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6751,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Wall oven","answerDisplayText":"Wall oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5352,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3253,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install in new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install in new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5277,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5276,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in new location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3253,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install in new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install in new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5277,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in same location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5276,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replace older appliance in new location","answerDisplayText":"Replace older appliance in new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500700,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the appliances for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the appliances for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/39763/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":39763,"taskName":"Appliance (Major Electric Appliance) - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Major Electric Appliance","xmTaskDescriptor":"Electric Appliance Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":140,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Appliance dishwasher fridge range stove","textMessagingName":"Inst Elec Appliance","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes electric washer, dryer, stove, range, refrigerator, dishwasher, freezer. Note separate categories for small appliances, water heaters, garbage disposers, HVAC equipment, audio-visual equipment \u0026 central vacuum cleaning systems.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes large kitchen \u0026 laundry appliances.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Major Electric Appliance.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Electric Appliance Installation \u0026 Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":3,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Major Electric Appliance Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Appliance (Major Electric Appliance) - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Appliance Project","urlName":"Appliance-Major-Electric-Appliance-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"Best \u003cspcount\u003e Electric Appliance Installation \u0026 Repair - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"dishwasher, fridge, range, stove, washing machine, washer, refrigerator, oven, dryer","emcCategoryOid":-12003,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":305,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}